# Lindani Nqabashe

- 063 841 3363
- lindaninqabashe@outlook.com
- 280 Gele Street, Hlongwane Section, Katlehong 1431

#### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

- Problem Solving
- Strong Communication
- Teamwork/Collaboration
- · Relationship building
- Conflict resolution



#### Career Objective

An enthusiastic versatile young person with an excellent attitude towards work. For the past two years have been a student at a largest ODL institute in South Africa that has taught me discipline and the ability to work as an individual or as part of a team.



#### **Professional Experience**

#### First National Bank

Software Developer Intern, Feb 2019 - May 2019

- JavaEE
- SonarQube(jaCoCo)
- Aquillian
- JUnit
- Mockito
- MySQL
- Hibernate
- · WildFly application sever

I was also part of the Prod-fest team that was responsible for solving all the logged incidents, problems and requests.

#### Makro

Shelf Packer, Nov 2015 - Feb 2016

I have worked at Makro through an agency called RPL. I was
responsible for shelf packing and sweeping under the shelf before any
packing takes place. We usually changed aisle on a weekly basis and
I have managed to a permanent worker within a month.



#### Education

We Think Code\_

Software Engineering, May 2018 - Present

I am currently a studying a we think code doing my second which is my last year from doing;

- C
- HTML
- PHP and MySQL.

Currently I am doing Java and Swift iOS.

### **Education**

## University Of South Africa BSc in Computing, Feb 2016 - in progress

- · Linear Algebra
- Introduction to Business Information System
- Theoretical Computer Science
- Introduction to Programming I
- · Computer System: Fundamental Concepts
- Introduction to Statistics,
- Visual Programming I and Human Computer Interaction I.

### Fumana Comprehensive School Matric Certificate(Bachelor), December 2014

• English(FAL)

- Mathematics
- · Physical Science
- Engineering Graphics & Design
- Life Orientation
- Information Technology
- IsiZulu(Home language)